Now moving forward in the list,
our next category is Investment Pack and
here I have chosen ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company and
I do not have any special subject to run this company, it is
just that
if you look at the entire sector, it is a very well-established
sector and going forward, in any way you
look at it, the penetration of insurance in India is
very low, awareness about it took a long
time but in the Corona period,
people will understand its importance,
how important insurance is and all
friends, if you look at planning also,
insurance has a huge importance, so
this thing should not be ignored
and going forward, you will see great
opportunities here, I cannot tell you if it will take 10 years,
but for one year,
I am seeing on the chart that by 2050,
you will see a very stable and peaceful and dancing growth of around 20 to 25 percent, ICICI
Lombard General Insurance, this is an investment from my side.